Where am I?
Oh, did I die again?
KONOSUBA
God's Blessing on this Wonderful World!
Episode 7
"A Second Death in This Freezing Season!"
After the battle with Verdia,
a leader in the Devil King's army,
the season turned to winter.
That day, I groaned wholeheartedly,
as if I were coughing up blood:
I want money!
Huh? Everyone wants that, obviously!
Anyway, you're entirely too unresourceful.
You make a goddess like myself
sleep in a stable every single night!
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
If you understand that,
then give me more luxury.
Spoil me more!
Do you not get why I want more money?
Huh?
Debt!
Thanks to the debt you've racked up,
most of the reward money we earn
from every quest we do is
deducted to repay those debts!
Just this morning... Just this morning,
when I awoke in the straw of the stable,
my eyelashes were frozen solid!
If I keep sleeping in that stable,
I'm going to freeze to death for sure!
I can't help it!
This city may have perished
in that battle with Verdia,
if not for my super astounding efforts!
You should exalt me more!
All of you should praise me,
praise me, and spoil me rotten!
You attention whore!
If your feats were that astounding,
then the rewards, accolades,
and debt are all yours!
Pay off your debts on your own.
Wait! I'm sorry!
I apologize for getting carried
away, so don't abandon me!
Why all the fuss so early in the morning?
Do we have some nice job lined up?
No, we haven't started looking for work yet.
Given the situation and all...
What'll we do today?
I'm sleeping at the inn. It's cold!
The reward for fighting off a
leader in the Devil King's army
was distributed to every
adventurer who participated.
There's no reason for anyone to go
hunting dangerous winter monsters
when their coin pouches are full.
I gladly welcome it, personally.
S-So do I.
The stronger the enemy, the better.
KO-NO-SU-BA!
The reward is well and good, but there
seriously aren't any decent quests...
Kazuma, Kazuma!
I'm Kazuma.
How about this?
A kill quest for a pack of White Wolves.
The reward is a million eris!
Just imagining a pack of wild
beasts making a mess of me...
Nope.
Kazuma, Kazuma!
Yes, I'm Kazuma.
How about this?
A kill quest for a One-Shot Bear!
Now is the time for me to
teach it which of us has
the stronger one-shot attack
with my explosion magic!
I want nothing to do with a monster
with such a dangerous-sounding name.
I bet we'd die instantly if it
so much as grazed our necks.
"The mobile fortress 'Destroyer' is approaching,
so we are recruiting scouts to
predict the route it will take."
What is this? What's a "Destroyer"?
The Destroyer is the Destroyer.
It's a massive fortress
that moves at high speed.
It lumbers around, trampling everything.
It's oddly popular with children.
I see. I don't get it.
Let's see. What's this?
A Snow Sprite kill quest?
Hey, what are Snow Sprites?
They don't sound all that
strong, based on the name,
but it says the reward is 100,000 eris each.
There are lots of Snow
Sprites in the snowy plains.
It's said that spring will come half a
day sooner for every one you kill.
Wow.
They're very weak monsters,
so they're easily defeated, but...
If we're accepting that
quest, I'll go get ready!
Hey, wait.
You're laughing?
Snow Sprites, huh?
Why does this masochistic crusader,
who always wants to fight strong monsters,
look so happy?
Still, money takes priority right now!
These are Snow Sprites?
Hey, can't you do something
about that outfit?
You look like some dumb kid going
cicada-catching in the middle of winter.
I can catch Snow Sprites
with this, and bottle them up.
I had the idea that if we mix
them in with our drinks,
we can have ice-cold drinks whenever we want!
Well? Aren't I smart?!
I can see how this is going to play out...
Darkness, what happened to your armor?
Are you going to be all right in that gear?
No problem.
I'm a little cold, but that in itself is...
I guess a pervert with steamy thoughts
has a high body temperature to match.
Kill Quest
Kill the Snow Sprites!
Number three, wait!
Damn! It's darting all over!
There!
I caught my fourth one! Kazuma, look here!
I caught a bunch!
If my kill count comes out too low,
I'll kill the Snow Sprites she caught, too.
Now!
Kazuma!
What?
Can I blow away all the ones in
the area with explosion magic?
All right! Wipe them all out!
Roger!
By my efflux of deep crimson,
topple this white world!
Explosion!
Hey, are you all right?
I got eight of them.
That makes nine defeated Snow Sprites total.
I even went up a level.
Oh, nice going!
It would've been a little cooler if you
weren't buried in the snow, though.
What the heck?
Killing Snow Sprites is totally delectable!
Why doesn't everybody do this?
There it is!
Huh?
Wh-What is that?!
So exciting...
Sh-She's playing dead...
Kazuma!
I'll tell you why adventurers don't
accept Snow Sprite kill quests.
Huh?
You lived in Japan,
so I'm sure you've at least heard the name
in the news and weather forecasts.
He's the Snow Sprites' master,
and is also said to evoke the image of winter...
Yes,
the Winter Shogun has arrived!
Th-The Winter Shogun!
One of the specially designated monsters
the country has put a huge bounty on!
Huh?!
I'm sure this monster plans
to use his position as shogun
to have his way with me.
I'll resist him,
but he will likely be beyond my
capabilities, and I'll be shamed...
Stupid!
Everything in this good-for-nothing world,
the people, the food, and the monsters,
are all absolutely stupid!
M-My sword!
Sprites pick up the subconscious
thoughts of the people they encounter
and take their form.
But the only ones strolling
around outside town
in winter are mostly just cheat-users
who came here from Japan.
So this guy was brought to life by some
idiot who came here from Japan,
whose train of thought associated
winter with the Winter Shogun?!
Talk about a pain in the ass!
When this is over, I'm gonna step on the girl
who's been playing dead this whole time.
Kazuma!
What is it?!
The Winter Shogun is generous.
If we politely apologize, he'll overlook this!
Prostrate yourself!
Prostrate yourself before him!
Come on, everyone, toss your
weapons aside and bow down!
Apologize! You hurry up
and apologize too, Kazuma!
The former-something-or-other who appears
to have abandoned all of her pride
prostrated herself quite
magnificently, indeed.
Hey, hurry and bow your head, too!
There may be nobody watching,
but a knight such as myself would
never bow her head to a monster.
You try to go off with monsters
willingly all the time!
Don't show off your pointless
pride only at times like these!
S-Stop it!
You're forcing me to bow my
head when I don't want to,
and shoving my face into the ground!
Huh?
What a reward!
The snow is so cold...
Kazuma!
Your weapon, your weapon!
Hurry and throw down the
sword you're holding!
That's right.
I was killed by the Winter Shogun.
Satou Kazuma-san.
Welcome to the afterlife.
I am Eris, the goddess who will
lead you down a new path.
Your life in this world is now over.
This feels familiar.
Is this how it was when I met Aqua, too?
Are you a goddess of this world?
Yes. Satou Kazuma-san,
you came all the way from
peaceful Japan to this world,
only for this to happen to you...
What's with this goddess?
Is she sincerely mourning my death?
She's not like that useless goddess!
Brave hero who came from a parallel world...
Y-Yes?
With my power,
I shall have you reincarnated in
peaceful Japan, to an affluent family,
and will make sure you
lead a life of comfort.
Huh? You can do that?
If you wish it.
Seriously?!
I-If possible, I'd like
above-average parameters in
charm, wisdom, and strength,
and I'd be even happier in a life where
a beautiful girl is my childhood friend!
Um, that is more than I can...
Wow, thank goodness!
I thought it was all over,
but now it feels like I pulled
through by the skin of my teeth.
This is a reward for trying my hardest, right?
Because my life up to now had been so awful!
Yes.
I looked in on your life
from time to time myself.
I believe your days were
filled with adversity.
You said it!
I reincarnated thinking I'd get to go on
a thrilling adventure, like in a game.
This is like a misleading promo video, isn't it?
The useless goddess who came
with me as a reincarnation perk
was just an arrogant good-for-nothing.
We recruited allies,
but the only ones who turned up were a crazy
explosion girl who fell flat
every time she used magic,
and a masochistic,
perverted crusader whose attacks always missed.
I was an adventurer,
but I did construction, side jobs,
and was forced into cabbage hunting.
I was in debt deep enough to sell an
organ after defeating a boss enemy.
Sleeping in the stables didn't restore my
strength, it only froze me nearly to death.
Do you know how it feels to have your
eyelashes frozen solid every morning?
The previous world's game balance
was beyond terrible, if you ask me.
H-Huh?
Why?
After you've been reborn,
may you be blessed once
more with kind encounters.
I see.
It appears
I was unexpectedly fond of
that good-for-nothing world
that I thought I hated...
I wanted to adventure with
those girls a little longer.
Now, return to us, Kazuma!
Huh?!
How could you get killed off so easily?
It's too soon for you to die!
Wh-What?!
Th-This voice... Aqua-senpai?!
Is it really you?!
Hey, Kazuma, can you hear me?
I cast recovery magic on your body,
so you can come back to this side now.
Oh, for real?!
P-Please wait a moment!
You've been reborn once already,
so according to the laws of Heaven,
you can't be revived again!
Is that true?
Aqua!
She says that according to the
laws of Heaven or whatever,
I can't be revived again since
I've been reborn once before!
Huh? What goddess is spouting that nonsense?
Hey, you! Identify yourself!
Where does a goddess in charge of a
backwater like this get off talking to me,
an elite in charge of Japan, that way?!
Hey, knock it off!
The face of the goddess in charge
of that backwater is twitching now!
Um,
she's a goddess called "Eris"...
Eris?!
The overrated Eris who's grown cocky
and even became a unit of currency,
just because she's worshiped a little
in the established religion of this world?
Hey, Kazuma!
Yes?
If Eris gives you any more trouble,
I'll confiscate her breast pads—
I-I understand!
Pads?
An exception! I'll deem this an exception!
I'll open the gate right now!
They're pads?
My goodness,
Aqua-senpai is as unreasonable as ever.
They're really pads?!
KONOSUBA!
I don't mind if they're pads.
You have now been connected
to the living world.
This normally never happens, you know.
You are called Kazuma-san, correct?
Huh? Oh, uh, yes!
This is our little secret, okay?
...zuma! Kazuma, please wake up!
Kazuma!
Oh, you're finally awake?
Sheesh, that girl's so hard-headed.
Kazuma!
Th-This is kind of extremely embarrassing.
Hey, come on, Kazuma.
What're you blushing for? Say something!
I brought you back to life, you know.
Don't you have something to say?
Come on.
I want to trade this useless goddess
for that cute goddess from earlier.
Say something.
Like words of gratitude, or an apology
for how you've treated such a
high-class goddess with such
contempt all this time...
Goddess change!
Fine, you damn NEET!
Why don't I send you to
meet Eris right away, then?!
N-Now, now, calm down, Aqua!
How do you feel?
Do you feel strange in any way?
It looks like I'm all right for now.
You are?
You were killed in such a
terrible way, after all...
Huh?
H-How was I killed?
You were beheaded by the Winter Shogun.
It was quite a splendid slice.
B-Beheaded?!
Winter in this world is
a season where only those who make
it through the struggle for survival,
despite the scarce food and harsh environment,
are allowed to remain alive and active.
There aren't any quests beginners
like us can complete easily.
Okay, retreat!
Kill The Snow Sprites!
Kill Quest
Retired
KONOSUBA!
Ta-da!
A Snow Sprite?
I didn't only prostrate myself.
I pretended to set them all
free, but I saved just one.
I guess even the Winter Shogun couldn't
see through my convincing performance!
Way to go, Aqua!
All right, hand it over and I'll kill it.
What?! No!
I'm going to take this one home
and make it a refrigerator!
The reward for killing those is 100,000 each!
No! Not this one!
I've already given it a name!
I won't let you kill it!
Don't! Don't!
She's resisting more than I expected.
Let her be, Kazuma.
Oh, fine.
I'll raise it with care,
and when summer comes,
I'll have it make lots of ice.
Then we'll open a snow cone shop!
We'll sleep together on hot, restless nights.
Hey, what does this little one eat?
Do Snow Sprites eat anything to begin with?
They look so fluffy and soft.
I bet if you put some sugar on it and took
a bite, it'd actually be really tasty.
I-I won't let you eat it!
Actually, I've worked up an appetite.
Let's order something!
I wonder what I should choose.
That goddess...
She mourned my death so much,
and smiled kindly when I was revived.
This is our little secret, okay?
A righteous, beautiful
girl who's not an oddball!
Finally, so long after I came to this world, the main heroine has appeared!
Kazuma, aren't you going to eat?
Huh?
Hey, how much did you guys order?!
Once you become as great a magician as I am,
you require great sacrifices
in order to function.
What's with you?
What is it?!
I brought you back to life today, Kazuma!
Huh?
There's nothing wrong with a
reward of this size, is there?
I put a little of the reward
from the quest into it, too!
That money was to get us through the winter!
What's the problem?
What?!
If we run out of money, we can
just accept another quest.
What sort of monster would be good next?
Maybe one that secretes a lot of slime,
or one with repulsive tentacles?
Just imagining it makes me
quiver with excitement!
On second thought, I should've
reincarnated in Japan.
I made the wrong choice...
The magician of extraordinary genius: Megumin.
Beneath her charming exterior lay tremendous explosion magic,
which was of such splendor, it was even artistic.
She brought tears to the eyes of everyone,
from children to the elderly, and even to wicked monsters.
Spectators rushed in from around to the world to catch a glimpse
of her wonderful magic, to the extent it became a subject of public concern.
Record of the Great Magician - Chapter 126
Episode 8
A Loving Hand for Our Party When We Can't Make It Through Winter!